HI.
HI, YEAH, HI.
I'M, UM, PHOEBE BUFFAY
AND I HAVE BABIES
COMING OUT OF ME.
OKAY. HAVE YOU STARTED
HAVING CONTRACTIONS?
NOT YET. I HEARD
THEY REALLY HURT.
DO THEY HURT?
OH. WELL...
OH, MY GOD.
NOW, WHICH OF YOU
IS THE FATHER?
NO, NONE OF THEM ARE THE FATHER.
THE FATHER IS MY BROTHER.
OKAY.
I AM SO GOING TO MISS
WATCHING YOU FREAK
PEOPLE OUT LIKE THAT.
( giggling )
OKAY, PHEEBS, LOOK, LOOK,
THIS IS FOR THE BABIES
TO LOOK AT SOMEDAY.
SO IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO SAY--
YOU KNOW,
BEFORE IT ALL STARTS?
OH, OKAY.
UM... HI, KIDS.
UM, IT'S ME, AUNT PHOEBE.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
HEY, WHAT TOOK
YOU GUYS SO LONG?
YOUR CAB LEFT WHEN OURS DID.
( clears throat )
WELL, WE HAD TO GO BACK
'CAUSE I FORGOT MY JACKET.
( chuckling ):
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU... YOU'RE NOT
WEARING A JACKET.
OH, MAN. I DID IT AGAIN.
OKAY, SO SOMEONE HAS
TO CALL FRANK AND ALICE
AND THEN MY MOM...
JOEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, I GOT TO GET
THE "BEFORE" SHOT.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU ♪
♪ LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HI. PHEEBS? OKAY,
SO WE JUST SPOKE TO THE NURSE
AND THE REASON THAT
YOUR DOCTOR IS LATE
IS BECAUSE, UH,
SHE'S NOT COMING.
WHAT?!
APPARENTLY, SHE FELL IN
THE SHOWER AND HIT HER HEAD.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE'S SO STUPID.
PHEEBS. PHEEBS,
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
I DON'T SEE THREE KIDS
COMING OUT OF YOUR VAGINA.
HONEY, LISTEN,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE NURSE SAID THAT
THE DOCTOR IS WONDERFUL.
YEAH, HE'S THE HEAD
OF THE DEPARTMENT.
( sighs ):
ALL RIGHT.
OOH. OH, DEAR GOD, SAVE ME.
WHAT?
I'M HAVING
MY FIRST CONTRACTION.
OH, IT'S NOT BAD.
Chandler:
OKAY.
( deep voice ):
AND SO THE MIRACLE
OF BIRTH BEGINS AND...
( screaming )
HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
OOH. SOMETHING HURTS.
OOH, IT'S SYMPATHY PAINS.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I DIDN'T KNOW
I CARED THAT MUCH.
HELLO.
HI.
PHOEBE, I'M DR. HARAD.
I'M GOING TO BE
DELIVERING YOUR BABIES.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW YOU'RE
GOING TO BE IN GOOD HANDS.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS
FOR A LONG TIME.
I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE
TO DO YOUR INTERNAL.
IN THE MEANTIME, JUST RELAX
BECAUSE EVERYTHING HERE
LOOKS GREAT.
AND, ALSO, I LOVE FONZIE.
DID HE JUST SAY
HE LOVES FONZIE?
THAT'S WHAT
IT SOUNDED LIKE.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY!
( all yelling )
HEY, AM I LATE? AM I LATE?
NOBODY CAME OUT YET, RIGHT?
NO, NO, NO,
WE HAVEN'T STARTED YET.
WHERE'S ALICE?
UH, DELAWARE.
SHE'S ON HER WAY, THOUGH.
SO UNTIL SHE GETS HERE,
I'M GOING TO BE YOUR COACH.
BUT DON'T WORRY-- SHE TOLD ME
ALL ABOUT THE "LA-MAZDA" STUFF.
YEAH, THAT'S WHEN,
IF YOU GET THE BABIES OUT
BY THE END OF THE MONTH
THEY GIVE YOU
TWO PERCENT FINANCING.
YEAH.
MONICA, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE VERY PROUD OF ME.
I JUST GOT US DATES WITH
TWO UNBELIEVABLY CUTE NURSES.
OH, MY.
THEY ARE MALE NURSES.
( chuckling ):
NOT IN MY HEAD.
ANYWAY, THEY WANT TO TAKE US OUT
SATURDAY NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
UM...
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT? WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S BEEN TELLING ME
TO GET OVER ROSS AND MOVE ON.
I'M MOVING ON,
AND YOU'RE MOVING ON WITH ME.
COME ON. GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON
WHY YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
WELL, UM...
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME SOMETHING
THAT WOULD BE A GOOD REASON
AND THEN I'LL TELL YOU
IF IT'S TRUE?
WHAT?
HARDER THAN IT SOUNDS,
ISN'T IT?
OKAY, YOU'RE COMING WITH ME,
I ALSO TOLD THEM THAT
IF WE'RE STILL HERE
WHEN THEY GET OFF
THAT WE'LL GO DOWN
TO THE CAFETERIA
AND GET SOME JELL-O WITH THEM.
( deep voice ): YEP.
THERE'S ALWAYS
ROOM FOR JELL-O.
JOEY, HOW DO YOU MAKE
THAT DIRTY?
AH, IT'S EASY.
YEAH, I CAN DO IT
WITH ANYTHING.
WATCH. UH...
( deep voice ):
GRANDMA'S CHICKEN SALAD...
ROSS! COME HERE.
GET A SHOT OF THIS.
HEY, BABIES--
THESE ARE THE HEADLINES
ON THE DAY YOU WERE BORN.
OKAY, NOW,
GIRL BABY, TURN AWAY
AND, BOY BABIES...
CHECK IT OUT, HUH?
THIS IS WHAT
NAKED WOMEN LOOKED LIKE,
THE MONTH YOU WERE BORN.
ALL RIGHT, NOW LET'S DIVE
RIGHT INTO THE GOOD STUFF.
OKAY, I'M HAVING
ANOTHER ONE.
THIS ONE DOESN'T HURT EITHER.
OOH, YES, IT DOES. OW! OW!
OW! OW!
OOH!
OOH, I WAS KIND OF HOPING
THAT WAS IT.
HEY, WHERE ARE MONICA
AND RACHEL ANYWAY?
A COUPLE OF NURSES ASKED THEM
OUT; MAYBE THEY'RE WITH THEM.
REALLY? MALE NURSES?
YEAH. I WAS BUMMED, TOO.
SO THEY'RE
GOING ON DATES?
WHEN?
I THINK SATURDAY.
( screaming )
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
UM, SYMPATHY PAINS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
REALLY SWEET AT FIRST
BUT NOW I THINK HE'S JUST
TRYING TO STEAL MY THUNDER.
OKAY.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT HERE.
OH, YOU KNOW,
FONZIE DATED TRIPLETS.
THIS FONZIE PERSON
YOU KEEP REFERRING TO--
IS THAT, UH... IS
THAT ANOTHER DOCTOR?
OH, NO, NO.
FONZIE IS THE NICKNAME
OF ARTHUR FONZARELLI.
THE FONZ.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT THAT WEIRD,
IS IT?
IT'S VERY WEIRD.
I DON'T WANT SOME GUY DOWN THERE
TELLING ME I'M "DILATED-AMUNDO."
TO BE FAIR, HE DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE IMPERSONATING FONZIE...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
WHY ARE YOU DEFENDING HIM?
JUST GET ME ANOTHER DOCTOR--
ONE WHO IS NOT CRAZY
AND DOES NOT "FONZIE."
AGAIN, IT'S NOT THAT HE...
OH! OH!
OH, HEY,
THERE-THERE YOU ARE.
LISTEN, I-I THINK
THAT THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
OH, IS THIS ABOUT YOU...
YOU DATING THE NURSE?
YEAH. JOEY ALREADY TOLD ME,
AND I AM SO, SO FINE.
I MEAN, YOU AND I--
WE'RE JUST, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE NOTHING.
WE'RE JUST...
EH, GOOFING AROUND.
UM, ACTUALLY I WAS
ABOUT TO TELL YOU
THAT I WAS-I WAS
GOING TO GET OUT OF IT
BUT, HEY, IF WE'RE
JUST GOOFING AROUND
THEN, UH, MAYBE I WILL
GO OUT WITH HIM.
FINE. MAYBE I WILL, TOO.
HEY. YOU GUYS. LOOK WHAT I FOUND
IN THE... GIIIFT SHOP!
OH! OW! GET UP! GET UP!
OKAY, PHEEBS?
YEAH.
THIS IS DR. OBERMAN.
HE HAS NO STRONG
FEELINGS ABOUT FONZIE
OR ANY OF THE
HAPPY DAYS GANG.
HI. AND YOU'RE GOING
INTO WHAT GRADE?
I'M ACTUALLY
A FIRST-YEAR RESIDENT,
BUT I GET THAT A LOT.
YOU SEE, I GRADUATED EARLY...
UH-HUH, ME, TOO.
ROSS, MAYBE I SHOULD
HAVE SPECIFIED
THAT I'D BE NEEDING
A GROWN-UP DOCTOR.
OH, NO, REALLY,
I'M FULLY QUALIFIED TO...
SHH! DOOGIE, SHH!
DOESN'T ANYBODY
UNDERSTAND THAT I'M
GOING TO BE HAVING
BABIES SOON? HUH?!
GO! GO, LITTLE BOY, GO!
OH, YOU MADE HIM CRY.
MR. TRIBBIANI,
I'M AFRAID
YOU'VE GOT
KIDNEY STONES.
UH... WELL, WHAT ELSE
COULD IT BE?
IT'S KIDNEY STONES.
OR...
KIDNEY STONES.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE GETTING THERE.
OH, AND, YOU KNOW THESE BABIES
ARE VERY, VERY LUCKY.
THEY ARE? WHY?
THEY HAVE THE HONOR
OF BEING BORN
ON THE FONZ'S HALF-BIRTHDAY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
JUST TO CLARIFY...
I'M NOT FONZIE.
HONEY, YOU KNOW,
I JUST GOT TO TELL YOU.
I THINK THIS IS
SUCH A TERRIFIC THING
YOU'RE HAVING THESE
BABIES FOR FRANK AND ALICE.
NO, IT IS.
YEAH.
CAN I TELL YOU
A LITTLE SECRET?
YEAH.
I WANT TO KEEP ONE.
OH, I'M GOING TO
BE ON THE NEWS.
OKAY, PHOEBE. HONEY,
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T KEEP
ONE OF THESE BABIES.
WHY NOT? MAYBE I CAN;
YOU DON'T KNOW.
YES, YES, I DO KNOW--
FRANK AND ALICE ARE GOING
TO WANT TO KEEP ALL
OF THEIR CHILDREN.
MAYBE NOT, YOU KNOW?
SERIOUSLY-- THREE BABIES
ARE A HANDFUL.
MAYBE THEY'RE, YOU KNOW,
LOOKING FOR A CHANCE
TO UNLOAD ONE OF THEM.
I'D HATE TO MISS
AN OPPORTUNITY
JUST 'CAUSE I DIDN'T ASK.
PHOEBE, NO. THIS IS...
THIS IS INSANE.
OH, JUST ASK HIM.
WHA...? ME?
I CAN'T ASK HIM.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW INAPPROPRIATE THAT WOULD BE?
ALL I'M SAYING IS JUST
TALK TO FRANK, OKAY?
JUST... YOU KNOW,
FEEL HIM OUT.
NO. FORGET IT.
I AM NOT GOING TO ASK FRANK
TO GIVE YOU ONE OF HIS KIDS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
( sighs )
TELL HIM IT'S FOR YOU.
FEELING A LITTLE
BETTER, SWEETIE?
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
I WISH YOU HADN'T
SEEN ME THROW UP.
ME, TOO.
HEY. I JUST HEARD.
WHAT'S UP?
KIDNEY STONES.
NOW, ORDINARILY, MR. TRIBBIANI
WE TRY TO BREAK THE STONES UP
WITH SHOCK WAVES
BUT THEY'RE TOO CLOSE
TO THE BLADDER NOW
WHICH MEANS WE CAN EITHER
WAIT FOR YOU TO PASS THEM
OR ELSE GO UP THE URETHRA.
WHOA-HO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOTHING IS GOING UP, OKAY?
"UP"-- "UP" IS
NOT AN OPTION.
WHAT'S A URETHRA?
( whispering )
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
SO DID YOU ASK HIM?
NO. I HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO BE ALONE WITH HIM YET.
WELL, I'M KIND OF
ON A CLOCK HERE.
( chuckling )
OH, FONZIE.
YOU KNOW WHO I
ALWAYS LIKED? MORK.
UNDO IT, UNDO IT, UNDO IT.
FONZIE MET MORK.
MORK FROZE FONZIE.
YEAH. UM...
YES, BUT...
FONZIE WAS
ALREADY COOL...
SO HE WASN'T
HURT, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY.
HI.
HOW YOU DOING?
OKAY. THE DOCTOR
SAYS ANY MINUTE KNOW.
HEY, YOU KNOW
ALICE IS GOING
TO BE HERE SO SOON.
YOU COULDN'T JUST, LIKE,
DO ME A FAVOR AND, LIKE...
LIKE-LIKE HOLD THEM IN?
SORRY, FRANK. I'M KIND OF
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE LAST FAVOR
YOU ASKED ME TO DO.
HEY.
HI.
RACHEL...
UH, MONICA, THIS IS DAN,
ONE OF THE GUYS WE'RE GOING
TO BE GOING OUT WITH
ON SATURDAY.
UH, DAN, MONICA.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HELLO, DAN.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO SATURDAY NIGHT--
REALLY, REALLY!
SO, DAN...
NURSE, NOT A DOCTOR, HUH?
KIND OF GIRLIE, ISN'T IT?
CHANDLER...
NO, THAT'S OKAY;
I'M JUST DOING THIS
TO PUT MYSELF THROUGH
MEDICAL SCHOOL.
OH.
AND IT DIDN'T FEEL SO GIRLIE
DURING THE GULF WAR.
SURE.
AND, LISTEN, THANKS FOR DOING
THAT FOR US BY THE WAY.
SO WHY WAIT TILL SATURDAY?
ARE YOU FREE TOMORROW?
SURE. I'LL GET SOMEBODY
TO COVER MY SHIFT.
AW, GREAT.
HEY, UH, HOW ABOUT IT--
YOU AND ME, SATURDAY NIGHT?
NO.
ALL RIGHT. VERY GOOD.
OOH, THIS IS A BIG ONE.
( screams )
OH! GET THESE THINGS
OUT OF ME!
BREATHE...
BREATHE THROUGH THE PAIN.
( wheezing )
I WANT THE DRUGS, ROSS!
I WANT THE DRUGS!
I DO, TOO! I DO, TOO!
( both screaming )
YEAH, I LOVE YOU.
OKAY. BYE.
HI.
THAT WAS ALICE'S MOM. SHE SAID
THAT SHE LEFT FIVE HOURS AGO.
SHE SHOULD BE HERE BY NOW.
OH, HONEY, DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S GOING
TO MAKE IT ON TIME.
YEAH.
SO, FRANK... THREE BABIES.
WHOO! THAT JUST SEEMS
LIKE A LOT, HUH?
( chuckling ):
NOT TO ME.
YEAH, FAIR ENOUGH.
OKAY, YOU'RE
TEN CENTIMETERS.
TIME TO START HAVING
SOME BABIES.
I WANT ONLY THE FATHER
IN HERE, PLEASE.
WE LOVE YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
LOVE YOU.
BYE, DAN.
UH, BYE, MONICA.
UH... BYE ( babbling ).
ALL RIGHT. I NEED A CLAMP,
A STERILE TOWEL AND CHANNEL 31.
WHAT IS THAT?
♪ Sunday, Monday, Happy Days ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday,
Happy Days... ♪
OH, MY GOD!
OH, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S A GOOD ONE.
FONZIE PLAYS THE BONGOS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
IT'S TIME TO TRY PUSHING.
ARE YOU READY?
IT'S TIME TO TRY PEEING.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT! WAIT!
IT'S ALMOST TIME
TO TRY PEEING.
NOW, PUSH. THAT'S IT, PUSH.
NOW, JUST CONCENTRATE
ON PUSHING.
YEAH, HERE WE GO.
I SEE THE HEAD.
YES! IT HAS A HEAD!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S IT.
KEEP PUSHING. COME ON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THERE'S SOMEBODY
COMING OUT OF YOU RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S SOMEBODY COMING
OUT OF YOU, AND HE'S, HE'S...
THAT'S MY SON!
ALL RIGHT.
( baby crying )
HERE'S YOUR FIRST BABY.
YES!
YES! WE GOT
A BABY BOY!
( all cheering )
FRANK, JR., JR.!
OH! HOW DOES HE LOOK?
HOW DOES HE LOOK?
SO GROSS!
OKAY, YOU READY
TO PUSH AGAIN?
OH, I ALREADY HAD A BABY--
LEAVE ME ALONE.
OKAY, OKAY, COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
( screams )
YEAH! HA-HA!
LITTLE LESLIE'S HERE!
WE GOT ANOTHER ONE!
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE...
TWO CHILDREN.
HOW SCARY IS THAT?
COME ON, LITTLE CHANDLER,
IT'S TIME TO BE BORN.
COME ON, LITTLE CHANDLER.
YEP. ALL RIGHT,
HE'S COMING.
COME ON.
HE'S COMING. HE'S COMING.
( crying )
HEY, WHERE'S HIS THING?
CHANDLER IS A GIRL!
OH, GOD,
KINDERGARTEN FLASHBACK.
WELL, THEY MUST HAVE READ
THE SONOGRAM WRONG
'CAUSE THEY-'CAUSE THEY
THOUGHT IT WAS A BOY
BUT CHANDLER'S A GIRL;
CHANDLER'S A GIRL!
OKAY! KEEP SAYING IT!
AM I TOO LATE?
NO, NO. EVERYTHING'S OKAY;
EVERYBODY'S HEALTHY.
THERE'S 30 FINGERS
AND 30 TOES.
WE HAVE OUR BABIES?
YEAH...
OH. WE HAVE OUR BABIES.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU DID IT, MAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SEE THEM?
THEY'RE SO SMALL...
SO I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW.
GREAT.
SO ARE YOU REALLY GOING
TO GO OUT WITH THAT NURSE MAN?
WELL, YOU AND I ARE
JUST "GOOFING AROUND"
AND I THOUGHT, "WHY NOT
JUST GOOF AROUND WITH HIM?"
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'VE EVER LOOKED UP
THE TERM "GOOFING AROUND"
IN THE DICTIONARY.
WELL, I HAVE.
AND THE TECHNICAL
DEFINITION IS...
TWO FRIENDS...
WHO CARE A LOT
ABOUT EACH OTHER
AND HAVE... AMAZING SEX...
AND JUST WANT TO SPEND
MORE TIME TOGETHER, YOU KNOW?
BUT, IF YOU HAVE
THIS NEWFANGLED DICTIONARY
THAT GETS YOU MAD AT ME,
THEN WE HAVE TO, YOU KNOW,
GET YOU
MY ORIGINAL DICTIONARY.
I AM SO BAD AT THIS.
I THINK YOU'RE BETTER
THAN YOU THINK YOU ARE.
REALLY?
OKAY. SO IF...
KNOW WHEN TO STOP.
I SENSED THAT I SHOULD STOP.
MM-HMM.
SO, WE'RE OKAY?
YEAH. ALL RIGHT, I'M
GOING TO GO TELL DAN
THAT IT'S NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN.
DON'T DO THE DANCE.
RIGHT.
I THINK
YOU'RE MY FAVORITE.
WHICH ONE DO YOU HAVE?
I DON'T CARE.
HI.
HEY.
SO FRANK AND ALICE
WANTED ME TO TELL YOU
THEY'RE STILL OUTSIDE,
MAKING PHONE CALLS.
OH. BUT, UM, I MEAN
DID YOU TALK TO THEM
ABOUT... YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
UM...
( sighs ):
NO, HONEY.
OH, OKAY.
IT WAS A LONG SHOT.
HEY, YOU GUYS,
CAN I JUST HAVE
LIKE, A SECOND ALONE
WITH THE BABIES?
OH, YEAH, SURE.
YEAH.
( sniffling )
( crying softly )
( door closes )
SO HERE YOU ARE.
SEEMS LIKE YESTERDAY
I WAS TALKING TO YOU
IN THAT LITTLE PETRI DISH.
EVERYONE SAID
LABOR WAS THE HARDEST THING
I'D EVER HAVE TO DO,
BUT THEY WERE WRONG.
THIS IS.
WELL, I HAD THE MOST FUN
WITH YOU GUYS...
AND I WISH I COULD TAKE YOU HOME
AND SEE YOU EVERY DAY...
OKAY, I'LL SETTLE FOR BEING
YOUR FAVORITE AUNT.
I KNOW ALICE'S SISTER HAS
A POOL, BUT YOU LIVED IN ME.
OKAY, SO WE'RE COOL.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
OKAY?
LITTLE HIGH FIVES?
AH! AH! AH!
OH...
( baby cries )
WELL, IF YOU'RE GOING TO CRY...
( sobbing softly )
PHOEBE, WE ARE SO PROUD
OF YOU; YOU'RE AMAZING.
I KNOW.
DOES IT REALLY HURT
AS BAD AS THEY SAY?
YEAH. YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO TAKE IT.
SO, NOW THAT LITTLE CHANDLER
TURNED OUT TO BE A GIRL
WHAT ARE THEY
GOING TO NAME HER?
THEY'RE GOING TO
CALL HER CHANDLER.
KIND OF A MASCULINE NAME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
WORKS ON YOU.